https://www.aceoptics.co.uk/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Cookie Notice
Ace Optics uses cookies to facilitate e-commerce and to monitor website traffic. See our privacy policy for full details.
Menu
OpticsBinocularsSpotting ScopesStay-on-CasesEyepiecesDigiscopingMonocularsLaser RangefindersTripodsMonopodsAccessoriesMagnifiersNight VisionField CamerasWinged EyecupsTorchesCamerasInterchangeable Lens CamerasLensesFiltersCompact CamerasBatteries & GripsMemory CardsCases & BagsFlashgunsTripodsMonopodsFilmsAccessoriesGift VouchersSecondhandDigital CamerasFilm CamerasCamera AccessoriesLensesSpotting ScopesEyepiecesBinocularsMonocularsOptics AccessoriesLeicaLighting & FlashgunsTripodsBags & CasesSwarovski at AceBinocularsSpotting ScopesStay-on-CasesEyepiecesDigiscopingAccessoriesTripodsLaser RangefindersKowa at AceBinocularsSpotting ScopesStay-on-CasesEyepiecesDigiscopingAccessoriesLeica at AceBinocularsBinocular Cases & AccessoriesSpotting ScopesScope Accessories & CasesRelocation Sale
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give us when you use this website. Ace Optics is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following details as required for normal operation of the website and to process orders:
Name
Contact information including email address
We do not collect payment data on this website. This is data is gathered directly by Sage Pay or PayPal, our payment processors, at the final step of order creation
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Order processing
Internal record keeping
We may use the information to improve our products and services
Where we use any customer information for statistical analysis purposes, the data is comprehensively anonymised to ensure that no individual can be identified.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which is stored on your system by your web browser on behalf of a website you visit. If you agree to this, the file is added and the cookie helps us to analyse web traffic and remember your configuration settings. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to store your preferences and track which areas of the website are being used. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, without the cookies we use to track sessions and cart contents, website functionality will be greatly diminished and it won't be possible to create an order.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not share your personal information with third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so.
You may request details of the personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 2018. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Ace Optics, 16 Green Street, Bath, BA1 2JZ.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete or you wish us to delete any information that we hold about you which we are not required to keep by law for accounting purposes, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct or remove any such information, as requested.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
FRONTEND_CID
You sesssion ID on the server (Secure HTTP version)
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
OW_COOKIE_NOTICE
Used to enable us to know that you have previously accepted and dismissed our cookie notice
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
External Services
We also use Google Analytics for traffic analysis, site health monitoring and demographic reporting. You may opt-out of Google Analytics tracking for ALL websites using the browser extension found at the following page: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
The cookies created by Google Analytics have the identifiers DSID, IDE, _GA, _GAT & _GID. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where they have come to the site from and the pages they have visited. Further details of Google's privacy policies can be found at the following address: http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
© 2019 Ace Optics, 8 Belmont, Bath, BA1 5DZ
